Guide to the New York University Collection of Papyri, Ostraka, and Cuneiform Tablets MSS.559
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I. Papyri Fragments, 55 Linear Feet in 44 small flat boxes and 2 oversize flat boxes
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0545.07, 39 fragments 02 x 3 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0545.07)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0545.08, 39 fragments 01 x 03 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0545.08)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0545.09, 39 fragments 03 x 1 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0545.09)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0545.10, 39 fragments 02.5 x 3 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0545.10)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0545.11, 39 fragments 04 x 7.5 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0545.11)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0545.12, 39 fragments 05.5 x 5 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0545.12)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0545.14, 39 fragments 02 x 3.5 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0545.14)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0545.15, 39 fragments 01 x 1 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0545.15)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0545.16, 39 fragments 03 x 7.5 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0545.16)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0545.17, 39 fragments 01 x 1 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0545.17)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0545.18, 39 fragments 02 x 6 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0545.18)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0545.19, 39 fragments 02.5 x 1.5 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0545.19)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0545.20, 39 fragments 01.5 x 2 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0545.20)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0545.21, 39 fragments 03 x 3 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0545.21)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0545.22, 39 fragments 02.5 x 6 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0545.22)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0545.24, 39 fragments 01.5 x 1.5 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0545.24)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0545.25, 39 fragments 09.5 x 5 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0545.25)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0545.27, 39 fragments 02.5 x 2 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0545.27)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0545.28, 39 fragments 01.5 x 3 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0545.28)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0545.29, 39 fragments 05.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0545.29)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0545.30, 39 fragments 02.5 x 2 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0545.30)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0545.31, 39 fragments 02.5 x 1 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0545.31)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0545.32, 39 fragments 01.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0545.32)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0545.33, 39 fragments 02.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0545.33)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0545.35, 39 fragments 02.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0545.35)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0545.36, 39 fragments 03.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0545.36)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0545.37, 39 fragments 04.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0545.37)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0545.38, 39 fragments 04.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0545.38)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0545.39, 39 fragments 02.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0545.39)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0546, 18 fragments 20 x 22 cm (Box 40, Item P.NYU inv 0546)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0547, 18 fragments 02.5 x 10 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0547)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0548, 18 fragments 04 x 20.5 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0548)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0549, 18 fragments 03 x 5.5 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0549)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0550, 18 fragments 03.5 x 5 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0550)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0551, 18 fragments 01 x 01.5 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0551)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0552, 18 fragments 04 x 04.5 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0552)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0553, 18 fragments 01.5 x 2.0 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0553)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0554, 18 fragments 03 x 6 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0554)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0555, 18 fragments 02 x 1 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0555)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0556, 18 fragments 04 x 10 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0556)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0557, 18 fragments 08.5 x 11.5 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0557)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0558, 18 fragments 00.5 x 2.0 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0558)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0559, 18 fragments 02.5 x 7 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0559)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0560, 18 fragments 02.5 x 1 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0560)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0561, 18 fragments 00.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0561)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0563, 18 fragments 02.5 x 1 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0563)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0564, 18 fragments 01.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0564)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0566, 1 fragment 03.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0566)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0569, 1 fragment 05.0 x 46.5 cm (Box 41, Item P.NYU inv 0569)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0570, 1 fragment 05.0 x 44.0 cm (Box 41, Item P.NYU inv 0570)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0571, 1 fragment 10.5 x 08.5 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0571)
    Existence and Location of Copies
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 001
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0572, 1 fragment 18.0 x 14.5 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0572)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 002
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0573, 1 fragment 13.5 x 08.0 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0573)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 003
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0574, 1 fragment 19.0 x 12.5 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0574)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 004
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0575, 1 fragment 07.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0575)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 005
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0576, 1 fragment 05.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0576)
    APIS Number: NYU inv cairo 006
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0577, 1 fragment 17.5 x 09.0 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0577)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0578, 1 fragment 17.0 x 11.0 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0578)
    APIS Number: NYU inv cairo 008
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0579, 1 fragment 06.0 x 08.0 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0579)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 009
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0580, 1 fragment 10.5 x 12.0 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0580)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 010
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0581, 1 fragment 05.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0581)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 011
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0582, 1 fragment 06.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0582)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 012
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0583, 1 fragment 20.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0583)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 013
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0584, 1 fragment 04.5 x 09.0 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0584)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 014
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0585, 1 fragment 09.0 x 17.5 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0585)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 015
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0586, 1 fragment 11.0 x 08.0 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0586)
    APIS Number: NYU inv cairo 016
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0587, 1 fragment 05.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0587)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 017
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0588.01, 1 fragment 03.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0588.01)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 018.01
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0588.02, 1 fragment 02.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0588.02)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 018.02
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0589, 1 fragment 05.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0589)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 019
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0590.01, 1 fragment 12.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0590.01)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 020.01
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0590.02, 1 fragment 12.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0590.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0591, 1 fragment 11.5 x 07.0 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0591)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0592, 1 fragment 13.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0592)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 022
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0593, 1 fragment 04.5 x 09.0 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0593)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 023
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0594, 1 fragment 15.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0594)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 024
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0595, 1 fragment 09.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0595)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0596, 1 fragment 04.0 x 13.5 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0596)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 026
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0597, 1 fragment 17.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0597)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 027
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0598, 1 fragment 11.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0598)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 028
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0599, 1 fragment 09.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0599)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 029
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0600.01, 1 fragment 13.5 x 08.0 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0600.01)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 030.01
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0600.02, 1 fragment 00.5 x 03.3 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0600.02)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 030.02
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0601, 1 fragment 02.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0601)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 031
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0602, 1 fragment 02.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0602)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 032
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0603, 1 fragment 03.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 16, Item P.NYU inv 0603)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 033
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0604, 1 fragment 03.5 x 08.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0604)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 034
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0605, 1 fragment 11.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0605)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 035
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0606, 1 fragment 08.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0606)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 036
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0607, 1 fragment 05.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0607)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 037
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0608, 1 fragment 02.5 x 07.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0608)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 038
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0609, 1 fragment 09.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0609)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 039
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0610, 1 fragment 09.5 x 10.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0610)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 040
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0611, 1 fragment 05.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0611)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 041
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0612, 1 fragment 09.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0612)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 042
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0613, 1 fragment 06.0 x 13.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0613)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 043
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0614, 1 fragment 16.5 x 10.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0614)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 044
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0615, 1 fragment 10.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0615)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 045
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0616, 1 fragment 07.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0616)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 046
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0617, 1 fragment 03.5 x 07.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0617)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 047
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0618, 1 fragment 04.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0618)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 048
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0619, 1 fragment 08.5 x 18.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0619)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 049
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0620, 1 fragment 09.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0620)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 050
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0621, 1 fragment 04.0 x 10.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0621)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 051
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0622, 1 fragment 07.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0622)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 052
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0623, 1 fragment 09.6 x 06.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0623)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 053
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0624, 1 fragment 09.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0624)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 054
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0625, 1 fragment 02.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0625)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 055
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0626, 1 fragment 06.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0626)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 056
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0627, 1 fragment 02.5 x 07.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0627)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 057
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0628, 1 fragment 05.5 x 12.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0628)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 058
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0629, 1 fragment 09.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0629)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 059
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0630, 1 fragment 15.0 x 10.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0630)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 060
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0631, 1 fragment 05.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0631)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 061
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0632, 1 fragment 05.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0632)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 062
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0633, 1 fragment 02.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0633)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 063
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0634, 1 fragment 11.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0634)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 064
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0635, 1 fragment 07.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0635)
    APIS Number: NYU.inv.cairo 065
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0636, 1 fragment 09.0 x 10.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0636)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 066
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0637, 1 fragment 03.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0637)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 067
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0638, 1 fragment 10.5 x 08.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0638)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 068
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0639, 1 fragment 12.0 x 09.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0639)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 069
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0640, 1 fragment 07.5 x 08.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0640)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 070
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0641, 1 fragment 03.0 x 11.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0641)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 071
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0642, 1 fragment 05.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0642)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 072
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0643, 1 fragment 08.0 x 11.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0643)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 073
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0644, 1 fragment 02.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0644)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 074
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0645, 1 fragment 03.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0645)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 075
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0646, 1 fragment 04.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0646)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 076
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0647, 1 fragment 06.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0647)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 077
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0648, 1 fragment 04.0 x 09.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0648)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 078
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0649, 1 fragment 11.5 x 10.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0649)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 079
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0650, 1 fragment 04.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0650)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 080
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0651, 1 fragment 04.5 x 09.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0651)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 081
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0652, 1 fragment 14.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0652)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 082
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0653, 1 fragment 07.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0653)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 083
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0654.01, 1 fragment 06.0 x 07.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0654.01)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 084.01
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0654.02, 1 fragment 11.0 x 12.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0654.02)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 084.02
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0655, 1 fragment 05.0 x 08.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0655)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 085
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0656, 1 fragment 02.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0656)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 086
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0657, 1 fragment 03.5 x 08.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0657)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 087
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0658, 1 fragment 03.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0658)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 088
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0659, 1 fragment 07.5 x 07.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0659)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 089
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0660, 1 fragment 05.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0660)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 090
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0661, 1 fragment 04.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0661)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 091
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0662, 1 fragment 06.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0662)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 092
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0663, 1 fragment 14.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0663)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 093
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0664, 1 fragment 05.0 x 11.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0664)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 094
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0665, 1 fragment 20.5 x 07.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0665)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 095
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0666, 1 fragment 05.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0666)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 096
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0667, 1 fragment 01.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0667)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 097
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0668, 1 fragment 02.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0668)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 098
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0669, 1 fragment 04.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0669)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 099
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0670, 1 fragment 05.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0670)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 100
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0671, 1 fragment 11.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0671)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 101
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0672, 1 fragment 07.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0672)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 102
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0673, 1 fragment 20.0 x 12.0 cm (Box 40, Item P.NYU inv 0673)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 103
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0674, 1 fragment 07.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0674)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 104
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0675, 1 fragment 06.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0675)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 105
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0676, 1 fragment 05.5 x 09.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0676)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 106
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0677, 1 fragment 08.5 x 08.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0677)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 107
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0678.01, 1 fragment 21.5 x 21.5 cm (Box 40, Item P.NYU inv 0678.01)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 108.01
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0678.02, 1 fragment 02.5 x 01.0 cm (Box 40, Item P.NYU inv 0678.02)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 108.02
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0679, 1 fragment 08.0 x 15.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0679)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 109
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0680, 1 fragment 10.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0680)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 110
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0681, 1 fragment 10.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0681)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 111
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0682, 1 fragment 06.0 x 08.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0682)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 112
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0683, 1 fragment 05.5 x 13.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0683)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 113
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0684, 1 fragment 06.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0684)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 114
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0685, 1 fragment 02.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0685)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 115
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0686, 1 fragment 01.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0686)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 116
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0687, 1 fragment 04.0 x 11.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0687)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 117
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0688, 1 fragment 12.0 x 07.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0688)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 118
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0689, 1 fragment 05.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0689)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 119
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0690, 1 fragment 10.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0690)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 120
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0691, 1 fragment 05.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0691)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 121
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0692, 1 fragment 14.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0692)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 122
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0693, 1 fragment 13.0 x 10.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0693)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0694, 1 fragment 10.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0694)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0695.01, 1 fragment 02.5 x 12.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0695.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0695.02, 1 fragment 02.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0695.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0696, 1 fragment 10.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0696)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0697, 1 fragment 09.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0697)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0698, 1 fragment 06.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0698)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0699, 1 fragment 06.0 x 09.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0699)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0700, 1 fragment 05.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0700)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0701, 1 fragment 13.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0701)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0702, 1 fragment 11.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0702)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0703.01, 1 fragment 03.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0703.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0703.02, 1 fragment 07.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0703.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0703.03, 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0703.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0704, 1 fragment 20.0 x 11.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0704)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0705.01, 1 fragment 06.5 x 15.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0705.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0705.02, 1 fragment 02.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0705.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0706, 1 fragment 12.0 x 17.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0706)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0707, 1 fragment 12.0 x 13.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0707)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0708, 1 fragment 06.0 x 10.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0708)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0709, 1 fragment 21.0 x 13.5 cm (Box 40, Item P.NYU inv 0709)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0710, 1 fragment 09.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0710)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0711, 1 fragment 18.0 x 12.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0711)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0712, 1 fragment 10.0 x 11.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0712)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0713, 1 fragment 05.5 x 08.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0713)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0714, 1 fragment 11.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0714)